# Juan Francisco Lizarraga Luna

## **Profile**

Creative engineer with experience in projects from conception to development. Skills include analytical skills, teamwork, problem solving, adaptability and flexibility to the situation, software management. I would like to continue learning more about front-end development, software engineering, network installation or tester.

## **Education**

Information Technologies Engineer. Aug 2018 – Dec 2021

Polytechnic University of Sinaloa.

IT Technician. Aug 2015 – Jun 2018

Conalep 121.

# **Experience**

Front End Developer Jr. Jun 2021 – Dec 2021

Solemti.

Member of a team of developers where the role played was developer in the front-end area, allowing the development of different intuitive interfaces to facilitate the use of the user. The tools used were HTML, CSS, Bootstrap.

Front End Developer Jr. Jan 2021 – Apr 2021

Polytechnic University of Sinaloa.

Member of a team of 5 developers where my role was in charge of the design of the interfaces under the principles of nielsen heuristics, promoting an intuitive design for the user. The tools used were HTLM, CSS, Bootstrap, Angular.

Maintenance and Support Intern. Oct 2020 – Dec 2020

#### Conalep El Rosario.

Responsible for the maintenance and support of the institution's laboratory equipment. Repair of computer equipment, disk cloning, installation of network cabling.

Maintenance and Support Intern. Oct 2019 – Dec 2019

Polytechnic University of Sinaloa.

Member of a team of trainees in which the role played ranged from being the team leader to an assistant to provide maintenance and support services to different institutions.

# **Additional**

- Microsoft Office Tools Course
- CCNA Routing and Switching certification: Introduction to Networking
- CCNA Routing and Switching Certification: Basic Routing and Switching Principles



## Contact

- **El Rosario, Sinaloa**
- ① 694 118 1385
- jflizarragal@hotmail.com

# **Development Tools**

HTML	***
CSS	***
Bootstrap	***
Figma	***
UML	***
Scrum	**
Trello	***
GITHUB	**
JAVA	**
SQL	**

# Languages

Spanish ★★★★★ English ★★

#### Skills

- Attetion to detail
- Self-motivated
- Team management
- Adaptability
- Resolution problems
- Self-starter
- Fast learner

#### **Hobbies**

- Sports (Baseball, ping pong, chess)
- Travel
- Video games